TINASHE MUZENDA

+263-71-821-8456



tmuzendat@gmail.com



171 Musasa Avenue, Harare



SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated and experienced concierge with a passion for providing exceptional customer service. I have a proven track record of success in anticipating and exceeding guest needs, going above and beyond to ensure that their stay is memorable and enjoyable. I am confident that my skills and experience make me an ideal candidate for a concierge position. I am committed to providing the highest level of service and ensuring that every guest feels welcomed and valued. I also enjoy working with others to achieve common goals.

EDUCATION

Kutama College

Ordinary Level 2017 – 2020

Kutama College

Advanced Level 2021 – 2022

SKILLS

- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- Experience in managing budgets and handling financial documents
- Networking
- Client Relationship Management
- Customer service orientation and a genuine desire to assist others

EXPERIENCE

St Michael's Primary School

Junior Master Internship | June 2023 - July 2023

- Game Management and assisted in setting up equipment
- Organised youth games and assisted in being a referee.
- Prepare and distribute meeting agendas, minutes, and other relevant materials
- Handle confidential information and documents with discretion and maintain their proper organization
- Assisted in helping visitors and assigned them to their designated destinations

St George's College

Inventory Manager | August 2023 - September 2023

- Managed calendars, scheduled appointments, and arranged meetings and conferences
- Prepared and distributed reports, presentations, and other materials
- Handled confidential documents and maintained their proper organization
- Coordinated travel arrangements and accommodations for executives and guests

TINASHE MUZENDA

+263-71-821-8456



tmuzendat@gmail.com



171 Musasa Avenue, Harare



Westwood Youth Centre

Concierge | 2022 - Present

- Making occupants feel comfortable.
- Serving meals to everyone.
- Co-ordinating local cleanups and exercises to help the occupants to stay healthy.
- Providing laundry services and hospitality for guests. Collaborating with the housekeeping team to complete the daily cleaning schedules.

LANGUAGES

- Shona
- English

REFERENCES

Lillian Phiri

Nyaririlillian046@gmail.com

Gerald Chiposi

secretary@stmichaels.co.zw +263 773 288 365

Keith Peterson

praline@blissgarden.co.zw +263 778 740 044